## ANDRI REIMONDO TAMBA

andriraymondo@gmail.com | 0851 7445 2288

Jalan Kedung Rukem III No 34 Surabaya, East Java, Indonesia

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andriraymondo/ | https://andriraymond.site

## **PROFILE**

I am a graduate in Information Systems from Del Institute of Technology with a strong grasp of concepts and practical skills in software development and quality assurance. Over the past 2 years, I have delved into Quality Control in the technology industry, expanding my insights into quality standards and effective software development processes. Currently, I am seeking opportunities to join as a software quality assurance engineer, where I can apply my knowledge and experience optimally. Additionally, I am also interested in exploring roles as a system analyst and IT Support, as I believe that my technical skills and understanding would be valuable assets in these roles.

EDUCATION	
Information System 2017 – 2022	Bachelor degree at Del institue of Technology
	EXPERIENCE
June 2022 – Present	<ul> <li>Software Quality Control, PT AZlogistik Dot Com</li> <li>Creating Task RoadMap and Assigning Task, Monitoring Team and Guiding Team members</li> <li>Testing with Manual Testing and Automation Testing with Katalon Studio for website</li> <li>Created Test Cases, Test Plan, Flow Steps, and Bug Reports using Microsoft Excel/Google Spreadsheet.</li> </ul>
June 2021 – August 2021	<ul> <li>Web Developer (Intern), <i>Pak Tani Digital</i></li> <li>Designing and building an online shopping system. The purpose of building this system is to assist farmers in agricultural education and addressing agricultural issues. This system also features functionalities for farmers to sell their harvest, purchase agricultural necessities, and more.</li> <li>ORGANIZATION</li> </ul>
2017 – 2022	Member of Information System Students Association, <i>Del Institute of Technology</i> • Participates actively and assumes a role in the organization's activities.
2019 – 2021	Member of Education and Research Division Information System Students Association, <b>Del</b>

	<ul> <li>Participates actively and assumes a role in the organization's activities.</li> </ul>
2019 – 2021	Member of Education and Research Division Information System Students Association, Del
	Institute of Technology
	<ul> <li>Participate actively in summarizing learning materials for members, and learning resources in accordance with the curriculum.</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Takes an active role in delivering educational content to members of the organization.</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Organize technology introduction events for schools in the vicinity.</li> </ul>
2019 – 2020	Institute of Technology Del's Consumption Division, <i>Del Institute of Technology</i>

• Actively participates in managing consumption activities during all campus graduation and inauguration events.

## **CERTIFICATION**

- Certification Database Administration Inixindo (2022)
- Fundamental Front-End Web Coding Studio (2023)
- Mahir Membuat Website dengan Laravel 9 Coding Studio (2023)
- Belajar Dasar Dasar DevOps Dicoding (2023)

## **SKILLS**

- Good command of Microsoft Office Tools (Excel, Power Point, Words)
- Good command and understanding: SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, and PHP
- Good command and understanding: Katalon Studio and Selenium Web Driver
- Basic Next Js Framework
- Basic Laravel Framework